{
    "subject": "resource/Hans_Grundig",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Hans Grundig",
    "human_readable": "The name of Hans Grundig is Hans Grundig.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9709137082099915,
            "question": "Is Hans Grundig's name actually Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9693213701248169,
            "question": "What is the name of Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9286444783210754,
            "question": "What is known about Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9248924255371094,
            "question": "Does Hans Grundig identify as Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8808883428573608,
            "question": "Are there any famous people named Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8791351914405823,
            "question": "How common is the name Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8738915324211121,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Hans Grundig besides his name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677617907524109,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of someone named Hans Grundig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7945574522018433,
            "question": "Is Hans Grundig a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6706714034080505,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Hans Grundig?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Hans Grundig is Hans Grundig.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7528_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hans Grundig a real person?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7528_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of someone named Hans Grundig?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7528_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information available about Hans Grundig besides his name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7528_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7528_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents do mention Hans Grundig, none of them explicitly state that his name is \"Hans Grundig\". The name is only mentioned as part of a sentence or phrase in each document."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Hans Grundig, including his birth and death dates, place of birth, artistic education, and career. All the provided details are consistent with the query that states \"The name of Hans Grundig is Hans Grundig.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "it is a tautology.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}